thedamway.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy/ TermsOfUse - PotPieGirl.com

* * *

Hi! I’m Jennifer – known as ‘PotPieGirl’ online. Welcome to my blog! I just want to let you know that the posts here on PotPieGirl.com may contain affiliate links which means, at 

_no_

cost to YOU, that I might receive compensation if you purchase something through a link on my site. 

In the blogging world that’s called “affiliate marketing”, and it’s a very common way bloggers make money by sharing products they love (like I do). 

Yes, that’s how many blogs make money. 

For example, [_This blogger makes $50,000+ a MONTH with her blog_](http://www.potpiegirl.com/msoam) – blogging is a solid home-business idea for just about everyone.

Ok, on to the privacy policy, terms of use, and all that other fun stuff!

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, PotPieGirl.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting PotPieGirl.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

You should also be aware that PotPieGirl.com may make a commission for a purchase or action you make via a link on this site. While PotPieGirl.com is not paid to write any review on this site, some articles do contain affiliate style links that enable this site to generate income.

**Earnings Disclaimer**  
There are no earnings potential claims on this site. Any claims of income are not results of the typical reader. The “typical reader” will read an article here and then never do anything with the info explained or addressed. All results are unique and directly influenced by the individual person. No one can guarantee a certain income with internet marketing.

**PotPieGirl.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.**

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of PotPieGirl.com then you may contact us at our help desk – AskPotPieGirl.com or via “snail mail” –

Jennifer Ledbetter  
c/o Ace Web Results LLC  
7380 Spout Springs Rd Suite 210-239  
Flowery Branch, GA 30542
